Monira Islam

Summary

As a dedicated BSc Software Engineering student at Daffodil International University, I am equipped with a diverse skill set, including web development, digital marketing, and programming. Proficient in Bengali and English, I excel in data analysis, communication, and staying updated with emerging technologies. My experience includes 6 months of Facebook marketing with E24 and maintaining the WordPress website https://e24.com.bd/. I also create websites for affiliate marketing using WordPress.

Experience

09-03-2023 to present

E24.com.bd

Facebook Marketing Specialist

- Managed Facebook marketing campaigns, resulting in increased engagement and traffic.
- Implemented strategies to optimize ad performance and reach target audiences.

09-03-2023 to present

E24.com.bd

Website Maintenance and Development

- Maintained and updated the WordPress website https://e24.com.bd/.
- Developed websites for affiliate marketing using WordPress.

Skills:

- Programming Languages: HTML, CSS, Basic C
- Software Proficiency: Microsoft Office (Word, Excel, PowerPoint)
- Data Analysis: Proficient in data analysis and visualization using Excel
- Web Development: WordPress web developer
- Digital Marketing: Facebook marketing
- Languages: Fluent in Bengali and English
- Communication: Strong communication skills

References:

Md. Tuhin Molla

Founder and owner of E24.com.bd

Phone: +8801778955697

Email: mdtuhin.eng@gmail.com



Contact

Phone +880-16183-60986 Email moniraislam715@gmail.com Address Daffodil Smart City, Birulia 1216

Education

2023-present

BSc. In Software Engineering Daffodil International University

2021

Higher Secondary Certificate Raipura Goverment College

2019

Secondary School Certificate Seraj Nagar MA Pilot Model High School

Personal Qualities:

- Self-learner, proactive in keeping up with technological advancements
- Detail-oriented and organized
- time management skills
- Excellent teamwork and collaboration abilities

Language

English Bangla